{
    "question": "This text is for questions 7-8    ANNOUNCEMENT\r\nFor all Junior High School teachers\r\nPOSTER COMPETITION\r\nFriday, May 21, 2021\r\n1328 Scott Hall, 11 a.m. - 1 p.m.\r\nYour poster must be:\r\nOriginal\r\nColorful\r\nTheme:\r\nLet's protect ourselves from COVID-19\r\nStay Healthy By wearing Masks\r\nJudges:\r\nMr. Thoms Waldschmidt\r\nMs. Sylvia Hanson\r\n7.What is the onnouncement about?\r\nA.poster competition\r\nB.Teacher competition\r\nC.How to wear mask\r\nCOVID-19 pandemic\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p></p><p>a. poster competition</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p>cmiiw ya</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "14-cinta-is-a-married-b-unmarried-15-how-long-did-553",
            "question": "14. Cinta is...........    a. married b. unmarried\r\n15. How long did she work for a\r\na. 4 weeks b. 5 weeks\r\n16. Cinta studied at grammar scl\r\na. July 94 - July 97\r\nb. July 93 - Oct 93\r\n17. Where did she work forin Jul\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>14 b</p><p>15 a</p><p>16 b</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>no 17 tidak ada pilihan ganda nya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "change-these-reported-speech-into-direct-speech-1-she-said-she-h-916",
            "question": "Change these Reported Speech into Direct Speech    1. She said she had never seen a comet.\r\n\r\n 2. They said it had been a wonderful time.\r\n\r\n 3. My father asked me who I played with.\r\n\r\n 4. He told us he was going to do judo\r\n\r\n 5. He told me he had to help his father.\r\n\r\n Change the Direct Speech into Reported Speech\r\n\r\n 1. Mum asked : \"Have you got the keys?\"\r\n\r\n 2. He said ; \"You should listen to the teacher.\"\r\n\r\n 3. The police : \"Don't park here!\"\r\n\r\n 4. Susan : \"Who has drunk the water?\"\r\n\r\n 5. They asked : \"Why didn't you play with us?\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Reported to Direct:</p><p></p><p>1. \"I had never seen a comet,\" she said.</p><p>2. \"It has been a wonderful time,\" they said.</p><p>3. My father asked me, \"Who did you play with?\"</p><p>4. \"I&#039;m going to do judo,\" he told us.</p><p>5. He said, \"I have to help my father\"</p><p></p><p>Direct to Reported:</p><p>1. My mum asked me if I got the keys.</p><p>2. He told me that I should listen to the teacher.</p><p>3. The police said to not park here.</p><p>4. Susan asked who had drunk the water.</p><p>5. They asked me why I didn&#039;t play with them.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "12-they-will-be-here-soon-the-word-they-refers-to-a-nabil-385",
            "question": "12. They will be here soon. The word they refers to ....    A. Nabil and Jaka\r\nB. Jaka and Mrs. Maya\r\nC. Jaka and Gita\r\nD. Erigo and Gita\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C Jaka dan Gita</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pilihan-alat-transportasi-saat-ini-sangat-banyak-alat-transporta-138",
            "question": "Pilihan alat transportasi saat ini sangat banyak. Alat transportasi yang paling tepat    dipilih ketika bepergian jauh lintas pulau adalah .... dibantu ya kak\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Pesawat</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu ya kak...</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>kapal dan pesawat</p><p></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-did-you-say-to-compare-animal-258",
            "question": "How did you say to compare animal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>The elephant is bigger than the tiger</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "explaining-yaur-self-when-in-the-past-tense-141",
            "question": "Explaining yaur self when in the past tense",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>i was a very bad person</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kalo salah sori cuk</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "nadine-mango-or-pineapple-angel-i-like-pineapp-395",
            "question": "Nadine : \"..... mango or pineapple?\"    Angel\u00a0 \u00a0: \"I like\u00a0pineapple.\"\r\n\r\nFill in the blank, with correct question is .....\r\n\r\na.\r\n\r\nWhich one\r\n\r\nb.\r\n\r\nWhich one Angel likes\r\n\r\nc.\r\n\r\nWhich fruit do you like\r\n\r\nd.\r\n\r\nChoose\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C. which fruit do you like</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Mungkin c (which fruit do you like) kak </p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p>semoga membantu:)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "b-write-ab-or-c-tulislah-ab-atau-c-1-my-hobby-is-me-259",
            "question": "B. Write a,b, or c ( Tulislah a,b atau c)!    1. My hobby is ... (Memasak)\r\n2. Two mother is meaning ...\r\n3. Teacher How are you?\r\nStudent\r\nThank you\r\n4. Anggur is\r\n5. Cat eats\r\n6. I like playing football\r\nFootball is\r\n7. Empat pisang kuning is.\r\n8. Indonesian flag is ..... And\r\n9. Teacher Riri is my English\r\n(Guru)\r\n10. Father is\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> 1. Cooking</p><p></p><p>2. Step mother / second mother</p><p></p><p>3. I&#039;m fine, thank you</p><p></p><p>4. Grape</p><p></p><p>5. Fish</p><p></p><p>6. Sepakbola</p><p></p><p>7. There are four yellow banana</p><p></p><p>8. Red and white</p><p></p><p>9. Guru</p><p></p><p>10. Ayah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "my-study-room-beautiful-569",
            "question": "My study room..... beautiful\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>very</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf kalo salahhhhh</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>is</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>my study room <u>i</u><u>s</u> beautiful</p><p>artinya</p><p>ruang belajarku indah</p><p></p><p>terimakasih</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-write-a-procedure-text-akl-how-to-make-a-label-774",
            "question": "1. write a procedure text :\r\nAKL ( how to make a label)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. tulis teks prosedur :</p><p>AKL (cara membuat label) </p><p></p><p><strong>ini</strong><strong> </strong><strong>terjem</strong><strong>ahan</strong><strong> </strong><strong>nya</strong><strong> </strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>aja</strong><strong> </strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}